Guide to the Stanford Tape Collection ARS.0112
Archive of Recorded Sound
Stanford Tape Collection
1940-2007
Bulk, 1960-1980
ARS.0112
Archive of Recorded Sound
14 boxes: 317 open reel tapes (37 5" reels; 200 7" reels; 80 10.5" reels); 5 videocassettes; 7 video reels; 1 film (8mm); 2 compact discs; one binder
Historic music and speech recordings on open reel tape, made on the campus of Stanford University.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use. Contact the Archive for assistance.
Scope and Contents
The Stanford Tape Collection consists of historic music and speech recordings made on the campus of Stanford University. Many were used in the production of broadcasts by campus radio station KZSU. The Stanford Tape Collection is one of several artificially assembled collections at the Archive of Recorded Sound, and it overlaps considerably with many other Stanford-related collections. The majority of recordings are on open reel tape.
The spoken component of the collection consists of lectures, speeches (including a series of commencements), panel discussions, committee meetings, poetry readings, interviews and news reports. Faculty and aministrators include Richard Lyman, J.E. Wallace Sterling, Fred Terman, Wolfgang Panofsky, Carl Djerassi, Linus Pauling, Philip Zimbardo, Edward Ginzton (interviewed by Henry Lowood), Diane Middlebrook, Janet Lewis, and William Shockley (from his infamous 1971 debate). Visiting speakers include such figures as Muhammad Ali, Elie Weisel, Jane Goodall and Gunther Schuller, but there are many tapes from visiting lecture series featuring leading scholars in a variety of disciplines.
There are also several recordings chronicling the political activity on campus during the volatile 1960s and 70s, including actualities and accompanying commentary from rallies, sit-ins and demonstrations. Most tapes appear to have been recorded by KZSU, and are likely edited for broadcast. Among the events covered are 1968's Interim Judicial Body Old Union Sit-in, the Black Student Union Rally of 1971, a Laos Teach-In at Dinkelspiel Auditorium, also from 1971, and the Stanford Judicial Council trial of Michael Holman, one of eight student activists subject to disciplinary action and suspension following the disruption of a speech by Henry Cabot Lodge.
The other half of the collection is devoted to music-related recordings. There are performances of the Stanford Symphony Orchestra with conductors Sandor Salgo and Andor Toth, as well as lectures and performances by faculty such as Putnam Aldrich, George Houle, Harold Schmidt, Herbert Nanney, and Adolph Baller and the Alma Trio (although their provenance is unknown, there are in fact a number of recordings from him present). Many of these tapes are from Stanford's Music Department, including lectures from the Archive of Recorded Sound's Ed Colby, William Moran, Ted Fagan, and Barbara Eick. Several recordings were originally music library or class reserves (identified by their "M-t" numbers) and may contain little or no Stanford-related content. There are also recorded presentations from meetings of the Music Library Association and the Association for Recorded Sound Collections. Additionally, some tapes feature performances by touring or off-campus local groups, such as a concert of Indian music, the Ghana Dance Ensemble, and the Peninsula Symphony Orchestra.
Although there are some programs and other notes enclosed in tape boxes, most of the tapes are minimally annotated, and many appear to have been recycled, possibly with older material on other tracks. Over the course of time, some tape boxes and reels may have been mixed up as well (particularly within the Baller series). This may explain some confusing or conflicting information. Transcripts were apparently made of many recordings; however, their whereabouts are presently unknown.
Related Collections
Other related collections at the Archive of Recorded Sound include the Stanford Recital Collection (ARS0021), Stanford Speech Collection (ARS0022), Meyer Library Lecture Tapes (ARS0116), Preservation Master Tape Collection (ARS0097), Stanford Program for Recordings in Sound Collection (ARS0104), Roy A. Long Collection (ARS0086), KZSU collection (ARS0062), Stanford Marching Band Collection (ARS0089), Non-Commercial Disc Collections (ARS0033) and the Harold Schmidt Collection (ARS0120).
Indexing Term
Stanford University
- 1. Music and Music-Related
  - Putnam Aldrich, 1962-06-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Putnam Aldrich, Renaissance Aesthetics. M-t7-111/112, 1964-06-25; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 9)
  - Putnam Aldrich, Berkeley recital for STARS, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Alea II, The Stanford Ensemble for New Music, Martin Bresnick, director. Brecht/Weill, The Seven Deadly Sins of the Petty Bourgeoisie. Cubberly Auditorium [program enclosed], 1975-05-06; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
  - Association for Recorded Sound Collections (ARSC) Meeting, Palo Alto, 1976-02-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    Scope and Contents
    1. Thomas G. Stockham, Jr. - Restoring Caruso Digitally 2. William R. Moran - Discography: Why and How, With a Review of the Present Status of the Victor Project 3. Les Waffen - On the Home Front: American Radio Goes to War 4. Oliver Berliner - Seventy-five years of His Master's Voice and the Bark Heard 'Round the World
  - Bach. Goldberg Variations, Aria Variations IV, VII, X, XV, XVI, XXX. Well Tempered Clavier: Prelude and Fugue II in C minor, IV in C Sharp Minor, V in D Major; Well Tempered Clavier, Prelude and Fugue VIII. St. Matthew Passion - Opening Chorus, Come Ye Daughters, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Bach. St. Matthew Passion, #33 Behold my Savior, #36 A, Now is my Savior Gone; St. Matthew Passion #75-78, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Adolph Baller, Alma Trio, etc.
    - Alma Trio, Mozart C Major, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Alma Trio, Brahms, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Alma Trio - Ravel, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Alma Trio. Baller, Wilk, Rejto. Schubert (RW), 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Alma Trio, Schubert, etc. Schubert, Trio in B flat Major, Op. 99; Beethoven, One Movement, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Baller and Rejto - Beethoven [Reel 1?], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Baller and Rejto - Beethoven Sonatas. Sonata In D Major Op.102 No.2; Sonata in A Major Op. 69. Montalvo. Reel 2, 1953-04-11; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Baller and Rejto - Brahms (Sylvia J.) (RW) #3, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Baller and Rejto - [Brahms?]; Schubert, Sonata in A; Bach, Brandenberg Concerto #5, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Baller and Rejto - Brahms, E minor Sonata op.38. Foothill Club, 1 10.5" open reel tape bent reel (Audio 10)
    - Baller and Rejto - Brahms E. Recorded in Living Room. tape box - Cinderella, etc., 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Baller and Rejto - Schubert; Brandenberg Quintette, Bach. Hokinson #1, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Baller and Totenberg #1, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Baller and Totenberg #2, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Baller, Wilk. Beethoven, Sonata for Violin, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Beethoven, Concerto. 1011, 1956-12-06; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - Beethoven Reel No. 792 [May 1958 desk calendar page enclosed], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Beethoven, Cello Sonatas op. 5 and op. 102 (Baller, piano; Rejto, cello); Beethoven trios op. 1 and op. 11 (Alma Trio: Roman Totenberg, violin; Adolph Baller, piano; Gabor Rejto, cello). dubs from Allegro Records AL50 and 34 [gift of Al Block], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
    - Beethoven, Violin Sonatas, op. 24, op. 30/4 (Baller, piano; Totenberg, violin). dub from Allegro Record AL47 [gift of Al Block], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
    - Beethoven, Cello Sonatas opp. 102/2, 69, 5 (Baller, piano; Rejto, cello). dub from Allegro Record AL75 [gift of Al Block], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
    - Roy Bogas #1, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Ray Bogas #1. Haydn, Andanti con Variazoni in F Minor. Brahms, Intermezzi from Op. 118 A minor, E Flat minor Op. 76 #3, Capriccio in B minor. Hokinson #1, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Ray Bogas #2. Chopin. Baller and Rejto. Sonata in G Minor, op.5 no.2; C Major 102; F Major 3. Montalvo, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - Debussy, Sonata for Cello and Piano. Adolph Baller, piano; Maurice Wilk, violin; Gabor Rejto, 'cello. Lent - Serenade - Finale, Anime. [date on spine illegible, 5/21/53? 55?], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Kodaly, Gabrieli, Chorus Rehearsal, 1 10.5" open reel tape pancake (Audio 2)
    - Edward Maragek (Baller's friend). Gallop, Schubert; Rondo D Major, Mozart; Minuet D Major, Mozart; Andante Esperanta; Grand Polonaise, Chopin, 1955-12-18; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Paganini, Violin Concerto, First Movement; Yehudi Menuhin, L.S.O. - Fistoulani. Tape No. 17826. Baller and Rejto, Quintet, etc. Reel 1., 1952-04-13; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - [tape box:] Schumann, Concerto. [reel:] Francis Whang. Kodaly, Liszt, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
    - [tape box back:] Francis Whang, Bach, Chopin. [tape box spine:] Whang, Kodaly, Liszt. [reel:] Rerecord Brahms for Rejto, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - Whang - Bach, Liszt, Schumann, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - Ballo Ensemble, The Renaissance Wind Band, The Early Music Singers. A Concert of Early Music. Dinkelspiel Auditorium [program enclosed], 1974-04-05; 1 video reel(s) (Box 12)
  - Barnes Orchestration, Dinkelspiel Auditorium. Dec. 6th, 1977; Dec. 9th, 1977. M-ta7-292-293, 1977-12; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 9)
  - John Boles - Living Room (slow), 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Bunkie Feagin (12); John Boles (warming up) (6), 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Alma Taylor - Mozart (2); John Boles - O Isis (5); June Thompson (10); Alma Taylor - When I…[illeg.] (4), 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
  - Brahms, Cello Sonata (One Movement Only) M-ta7 X 15:2 #2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Ed Colby. 75 years of Sound. For Stanford Faculty Women's Club, 1971-05-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Ed Colby, Beatles: Bachwards and Forwards, 1967-10; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 9)
  - Composer Visits. Stanford Program. Radio Project. M-ta10-506, 1960-08-09; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Barbara Eick, Music and Voices From the Past, An Evening of Historical Recordings from the Archive of Recorded Sound. Dinkelspiel Rehearsal Hall, 8:00pm [program enclosed], 1978-07-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Ted Fagan, Musicians on Music. Presented By The Department of Music and the Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound. Annenberg Auditorium, 8:00pm [program enclosed], 1979-03-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Founder's Day Concert, Choir, Organ. Sermon and Address, 1960-03-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Ghana Dance Ensemble. Reel 1-2, 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 4)
  - Hello Dolly, Ram's Head production. Copied from Cassette Master. M-ta10-2, 1987-11-05; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - Alexander Horak Compositions. Harp Sonatina by Ann Henderson. Concerto Piccolo for Bassoon And Piano by Fred Dutton and Naomu Sparrow, 1957; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    Correspondence from Horak to Ed (Colby?) enclosed, dated 2/16/63. Both compositions written at Stanford in 1957.
  - Prof. Horsely, Music 101. Fall 1975. Special Paper, Peri, Monteverdi, 1 5" open reel tape(s) (Audio 6)
  - Prof. Horsely, Music 101. Fall 1975. Peri, Monteverdi, 1 5" open reel tape(s) (Audio 6)
  - Prof. Horsely, Music 101. Fall 1975. Monteverdi, 1 5" open reel tape(s) (Audio 6)
  - George Houle, etc. Sonatas, Suites, Cantatas, etc. M-t7-107, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Lamento di Tristan [Stanford Music Library stamp], 1 5" open reel tape(s) (Audio 6)
  - Meredith Little, Music 269c Class performances, 1973-03-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - McClintock, Institute of Renaissance Music. Some Aspects of Musical Performance at Ferra And Machua During the High Renaissance, 1964-07-16; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - Memorial Church services
    - Christmas Service of Lessons and Carols, Memorial Church. 12/12-13/1980 [program enclosed], 1980-12; 3 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 11)
    - Memorial Church Services. University Public Worship 11/8/1981; Twentieth-Third Sunday After Pentecost 11/15/1981; Thanksgiving 11/22/1981; First Sunday of Advent 11/29/1981 [programs enclosed], 1981-11; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 11)
    - Memorial Church Services. Second Sunday of Advent 12/6/1981; End of Quarter Christmas Worship Service 12/13/1981. [programs enclosed], 1981-12; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 11)
  - Messe de St. Hubert, Odeon. Notre Dame 1953. For Tours HCS. Also at end - Russland and Ledmulla for Exam. M-t7 Tou-5, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Music of India. A Concert by Lalgudi Jayaraman, violin; N. Ramani, flute; T. Ranganathan, mridangam. Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 8:00pm [program enclosed], 1971-10-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Music Library Association meetings
    - Music Library Association Summer 1967, Third Session - Don Krummel, M.C., 1967-06-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - Music Library Association Summer 1967, Pauline Oliveros, 1967-06-30; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
    - Music Library Association Meeting, Stanford. Gary Bowles, Chair. Panel - Music Bibliography. Vincent Duckles, Jon Emerson, Edward Colby, 1968-07-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Herbert B. Nanney, Organ recital, Stanford Memorial Church. Recorded by Harold Lindsay, 1953-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Herbert B. Nanney, Organ Demonstration Recital. Stanford Memorial Church. In both 2-channel stereo and mono 1953-07(2 reels), 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 9)
  - Herbert B. Nanney, Variations on a Swiss Carol (Organ), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Herbert B. Nanney, Ear training tape. Music 24, 1 5" open reel tape(s) (Audio 6)
  - Peninsula Symphony Orchestra, Sylvia Jenkins, piano. Schumann, Concerto for Piano and Orchestra in A minor, op.54. Hokinson #2, 1951-10-26; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - Peninsula Symphony Orchestra. Cinderella - a Phantasy. Eric Coates; Popular Selections, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - [Vladimir?] Pleshakov Final Project, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Poulenc, Stabat Mater. Dubbed from Three Channel for Close Soloist. M-ta10-92, 19uu-05-20; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Poulenc, Mass. 15ips, Mono, Tails Out, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Poulenc, Stabat Mater. Original Master, Not Dubbed from Three Channel. M-ta10-91, 19uu-05-21; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
  - Renaissance-Baroque Ensemble of San Francisco. George Houle, director. Renaissance Music for Voices and Viols. M-t7-108, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Gunther Schuller, Jazz: An Art Form? Bishop Auditorium, 8:00pm, 1972-05-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Gunther Schuller, Rock and All That Jazz. Leon Sloss Lecture Series, Kresge Auditorium. April 5-9, 1978. Reels 1-2, 1978-04; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
  - Marilyn Somville, Lute and Voice Demonstration and Lecture. Mt7-9/10, 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 9)
  - Stanford Music Department student conductors. Bartok, Piano Concerto #3, Layne Stramler, piano; Moussorgsky. Coronation scene from Boris Godunov. M-ta7 x58-3, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Stanford Music Department, Stanford Players. Sandor Salgo, musical director. Harold Schmidt, choral director. Prokofiev, Love for Three Oranges. M-ta10-513/514. Radio program concludes with pianist Walter Moore playing Debussy and Copland [announcer script enclosed], 1960-09-10; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 2)
  - Stanford Music Department sample radio broadcast, KBAY (with announcer and excerpts of performances by various campus musical groups), 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Leland Stanford Junior University - Marching Band Assembled Master Tape (L - 250 Dynamicron Video Cassette), 1 videocassette(s) (Audio 6)
  - Stanford Marching Band/Sierra Club - Star Spangled Banner, 1973; 1 film(s) 8mm, color (Box 6)
  - Stanford Men's Glee Club [song list enclosed], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Stanford Men's Glee Club. A Rough Catalog Concerning the Music of Robert MacKinnon, 1916- Composer And Arranger, 1 folder(s) (Box 12)
  - Stanford Summer Orchestra, Martin Fraile and Christopher Bowen, Conductors. Tiffany Cromartie, Soprano. Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 8:00pm [program enclosed], 2007-07-21; 2 compact discs (Audio 6)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra. Stravinsky, Oedipus Rex
    - Stravinsky. Oedipus Rex. Stanford Symphony. Salgo, conductor. Partial, Continuation, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Stravinsky, Oedipus. Original Master. May 20-21. M-ta10-96-97, 19uu-05-21; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Salgo, conductor. Searle, Symphony No.5, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Salgo, conductor. Schmidt, choral director. Douglas Moore, Ballad of Baby Doe. Second premiere, performed for opening of Dinkelspiel Auditorium. 570531 M1-M6, 1957-05-31; 6 10.5" open reel tapes (Box 12)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Sandor Salgo, Conductor. Stanford Chorale, Harold Schmidt, Director. KQED Concert Hall, Recorded at KQED [recent track list enclosed], 1961-05-19; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Salgo, conductor. University Chorus, Memorial Church Choir, Stanford Chorale, Schmidt, director. Music of Beethoven in Honor of Founders' Day 3/10-11/1974. Dinkelspiel Auditorium [program enclosed], 1974-03; 2 video reels (Box 12)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Martinon, conductor. Open rehearsal. Dinkelspiel Auditorium. Martinon, Tragic Overture; Bizet, Symphony in C, 1975-04-28; 2 video reels (Box 12)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra. Hail, Stanford, Hail, 1988-02-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra. Masters used in preparation for SSO Cassette, 1988-06-06; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 9)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Toth, conductor. Rehearsal Recorded by Singapore Television, 6/22-23/88. Angela Kyung Sohn, violin, Singapore Symphony Chorus. Barber, Violin Concerto; Beethoven, Symphony No.9, 1988-06; 1 videocassette VHS (Box 12)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Andor Toth, conductor. Victoria Concert Hall. Barber, Beethoven. Singapore Broadcasting Corporation dubs X35223/35225 [personnel and other details in list enclosed. see also videocassettes], 1988-06-23; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
  - Stanford Symphony Orchestra, Toth, conductor. Centennial Tour, Victoria Concert Hall. Angela In Kyung Sohn, violin, Singapore Symphony Chorus. Barber, Violin Concerto; Beethoven, Symphony No.9, 1988-06-23; 1 videocassette VHS (Box 12)
  - Stanford University Chorus and Orchestra, Schmidt, director. Memorial Church. Verdi, Requiem, 1975-05-11; 2 video reels (Box 12)
  - San Francisco Symphony, Stanford University Chorus. Josef Krips, conductor. Beethoven Symphony No.9. Choral Movement Only. Dub of poor quality in-house recording, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Stanford Wind Ensemble, Arthur Barnes, director. Stanford Studio Jazz Band. Dinkelspiel Auditorium 8:00pm [program enclosed], 1981-02-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Hal Stein, California Arts Council Artist in Residence. Dub from VHS, 1985-04-29; 1 videocassette Beta (Box 12)
  - Stravinsky. Suite no. 1; Faure. Pelleas. Unidentified live performance. M-ta7 x-17, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Student Composers Symposium at UC Berkeley. Stanford Composers. Dexter Merrill, String Quartet; Christopher Lantz, Wind Sextet 4/28/1961, 4/29/1961. M-t7-30, 1961-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Student Comp. M-t7-18, 1951-05-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - Sweelinck, Byrd, Palestrina, Bach. Choral singing with organ. Live, probably in Memorial Church. M-ta7 x34, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Randall Thompson, Ode to the Virginia Voyage. Unidentifed live performance, probably Stanford. M-ta7 x-68, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Virgil Thomson. Evening, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - University Baroque Ensemble under direction of George Houle. Three Romanescas. M-t7-106, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 9)
  - Anne Witherell, producer. Rehearsal for Concert of French Baroque Music and Dance. Wendy Hilton, Julianne Baird, Erich Schwandt, 1975-07-22; 2 videocassettes One VHS; 1 Beta (Box 12)
- 2. Spoken (Lectures, Speeches, Readings, Panel Discussions, Meetings, Hearings, etc.)
  - Muhammad Ali - Frost Amphitheater, 1971-05-21; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 5)
  - ASSU Presidents, 1971-05-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Bennett-Lewis P.O.W. talks, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Prof. Jackson J. Benson lecture on Steinbeck and Tom Collins. Stanford Library Association. Annenberg Auditorium, 1975-04-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Daryl and Sandra Bern Lecture, Training the Woman to Know her Place: The Power of an Unconscious Ideology, 1973-02-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
  - [Lyuba] Bershadskaya. Soviet Jews, 1971-02-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Black Student Union (BSU) Rally, Racism Convocation, 1971-05-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
  - Prof. Claude A. Buss, East and West. Memorial Auditorium, 1965-05-17; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 10)
  - Harry Camp Memorial Lecture series
    - Elie Weisel, Bibical Heroes: Our Contemporaries. Adam (ZZ407) Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 8:00pm. Harry Camp Memorial Lecture series, 1974-05-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Elie Weisel, Bibical Heroes: Our Contemporaries. Cain and Abel (ZZ408) Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 8:00pm, 1974-05-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - Elie Weisel, Bibical Heroes: Our Contemporaries. The binding of Isaac (ZZ409) Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 4:15pm, 1974-05-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 7)
    - J. H. Hexter, Foundations of Human Freedom, Camp Memorial Lecture. May 5-8, 1977. Reels 1-2, 1977-05; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
  - Commencements, Baccalaureates
    - Commencement, 1971-06-13; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
    - Commencement, 1976-06-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Commencement, 1973-06-17; 2 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Commencement. Archibald Cox, Richard Lyman, 1974-06-16; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 8)
    - Commencement, 1979-06-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Baccalaureate, 1978-06-17; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Commencement, 1978-06-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Baccalaureate, 1980-06-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
    - Commencement, 1980-06-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 8)
  - Committee Meetings/Hearings (Advising/Counseling, Steering, Admissions/Financial Aid)
    - Advising and Counseling 6/27/1968; 7/1/1968, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Advising and Counseling 5/12/1968; 5/21/1968; 5/28/1968, 1968-05; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Advising and Counseling. Hearings April 9-10, 1968; 2/6/1968; 5/7/1968, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Advising and Counseling 1/16/1968; 4/16/1968, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Advising and Counseling 4/23/1968; 4/30/1968; 1/5/1968, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Admissions and Financial Aid 3/11/1968; Computer Committee 3/14/1968, 1968-03; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Clark 5/13/1968; Admissions Committee 5/15/1968, 1968-05; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee, 1968-02-14; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Open Hearings - Agenda; Topic Committee, 1968-04-15; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Side 1. Open Hearings, Admissions and Financial Aid, June 1, 1967, 4:00pm. Side 2. Admissions and Financial Aid May 27, 1968, 1967-1968; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)
    - Steering Committee, 1968-05-30; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 6)